Guide to the Kevin Kennedy Ephemera and Photographs AIA.063
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Kevin Kennedy Ephemera and Photographs Collection
1916-2009
1971-2008
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Kennedy, Kevin
AIA.063
28.08 Linear Feet in 20 record cartons, 5 legal sized manuscript boxes, 1 flat box, 1 oversized flat box, and 2 shared oversized flat boxes.
Kevin Kennedy (1937-2016) was a native of County Galway in Ireland and worked as a photographer in New York City, contributing to publications like The Irish Echo. Kennedy was affiliated with Irish civic organizations like the United Irish Counties Association and the New York County chapter of the Ancient Order of Hibernians. He was also devoted to fundraising on behalf of the Irish Guide Dogs for the Blind. This collection consists of photographs, photo negatives, newspapers, magazines, newspaper clippings, social event programs, religious booklets, church related materials, artifacts, correspondence, and a scrapbook.
Scope and Contents
The Kevin Kennedy Ephemera and Photographs Collection is composed of materials collected by Kevin Kennedy that documents the New York Irish community, circa 1960s-early 2000s. The collection consists of photographs, photo negatives, newspapers, magazines, newspaper clippings, social event programs, religious booklets, church related materials, artifacts, prayer cards, correspondence, and a scrapbook.
Some of the materials found in this collection document important Irish civic organizations like the United Irish Counties Association, the New York County chapter of the Ancient Order of Hibernians, the Knights of Columbus, and the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick, as well as Irish charities important to Kennedy like the Irish Guide Dogs for the Blind and the Kennedy Child Study Center in New York City.
The photographs and photo negatives in this collection largely focus on events.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The materials in this collection were acquired from Kevin Kennedy's Manhattan apartment by Marion Casey in 2007.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in two series:
Series I: Kevin Kennedy Ephemera and Personal Materials
Series II: Photographs and Photo Negatives
Within each series, materials are organized in alphabetical order.
Biographical Note
Kevin Kennedy (1937-2016) was a native of County Galway in Ireland and worked as a photographer in New York City, contributing to publications like The Irish Echo. Kennedy was affiliated with Irish civic organizations like the United Irish Counties Association and the New York County chapter of the Ancient Order of Hibernians. He was also devoted to fundraising on behalf of the Irish Guide Dogs for the Blind.
Separated Materials
In 2021, Irish American newspapers and periodicals were removed from the Kevin Kennedy Ephemera and Photographs collection and placed in to the Guide to the Archives of Irish America Newspapers and Periodicals Collection (AIA.004).
Saint Patrick's Day.; Galway (Ireland: County); Mayo (Ireland: County); Offaly (Ireland); Louth (Ireland: County); Negatives (photographs); Color photographs.; Correspondence.; Scrapbooks.; Irish Americans -- Newspapers.; Irish newspapers.; Newspapers.; Artifacts.; New York (N.Y.).; Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.); Ancient Order of Hibernians; Friendly Sons of St. Patrick; Irish echo; Irish Guide Dogs for the Blind; Adams, Gerry, 1948-; Clinton, Bill, 1946-; Pataki, George E., (1945-); Koch, Ed, 1924-2013; Cuomo, Mario M., 1932-2015; United Irish Counties Association.; Cardinal Cooke Guild; Knights of Columbus
- Series I: Kevin Kennedy Ephemera and Personal Materials, 1961-2010 (inclusive); 1966-2007 (bulk); 6.41 Linear Feet in 5 legal size manuscript boxes, 1 flat box, 1 oversized box, and 2 shared oversized boxes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains materials collected by Kevin Kennedy that focus upon the New York Irish community, circa 1960s-early 2000s. Some of the materials document important Irish organizations like the United Irish Counties Association, the New York County chapter of the Ancient Order of Hibernians, and the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick, as well as charitable organizations that were important to Kennedy like the Irish Guide Dogs for the Blind and the Kennedy Child Study Center in New York City. This series also contains some religious materials including prayer cards and programs from different churches commemorating various events, as well as newspapers and newsclippings, some of which feature Kennedy's published photographs.
  - 55th Annual Feis at St. Joseph's Seminary, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Friends of James Joyce, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American-Irish Historical Society, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Apollo: "Arts in Ireland", 1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Apostolic Blessing for Kevin J. Kennedy, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Association of Knights and Ladies of the Equestrian Order of the Holy Sepulchre of Jerusalem, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "At the Crossroads of the World", 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ballintubber Abbey, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Blessed Edmund Rice Dinner ~ Dance, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bradford Exchange, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Brian O'Connor Benefit Dance Committee, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Business Cards, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Calendar, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Camera Manuals, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Cardinal's Christmas Luncheon, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The Catholic New York Newspaper Clippings, 1984, 1988, 2005 (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 9)
  - The Catholic News & Catholic New York Newspaper Clippings, 1969-2004 (Box Shared Tamiment 081, Folder 17)
  - Cathedral High School Band Program, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cathedral of St. Patrick, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ceremony of Installation - Terence J. Cook D.D., 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Chippewa Democratic Club Annual Dinner Dance, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Church of Saint Mary the Virgin, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Church of St. Brendan - Reverand Vincent Ciorciari, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Circulars, 1997-2010 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - City Council Citation for Mary Feely, 1995 (Box 6)
  - The Coast to Coast Walk Magazine, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Columbia - The Knight of Columbus Magazine, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Compiled in Loving Memory of Our Departed Brother Pioneer Joseph M. Costello RIP", 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Connacht Tribune Newspaper Clippings, 1969-1986 (Box Shared Tamiment 081, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1966-2007 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Michael T. Ridge, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - County Tipperary Association of New York, Inc., 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cuimhneachan, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "The Dock and the Scaffold", undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Dunmore Dance, Irish Echo, & Irish Voice, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Father Bart Daly (Sash), 1994 (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 14)
  - The Fiftieth Annual Alfred Emanuel Smith Memorial Foundation Dinner, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Gaelic Athletic Association of Greater New York and Central Council, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Galway Irish Crystal, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Galway Dance and "Western People" Contact Lists, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Galway Hurling Club of New York, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Galway Men's S&B Association, 1971, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Garden State Games Medal, 1983 (Box 6)
  - General Liam Lynch, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Geraldine Kennedy, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Grosse-Ile and the Irish Memorial, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Guidelines: The Magazine of Irish Guide Dogs for the Blind, 2004, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - The Herald Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1978 (Box Shared Tamiment 081, Folder 15)
  - The Installation of Father Daly, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Invitations, 1971-2005 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - "Ireland Chamber of Commerce in the United States", 1993 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Irish Advocate Newspaper Clippings, 1983-1989 (Box Shared Tamiment 081, Folder 20, Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 8)
  - Irish American Building Society, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Irish American Organizations, 1974, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - The Irish Echo Newspaper Clippings, 1986-2005 (Box Shared Tamiment 081, Folder 13, Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 11)
  - The Irish Answer Magazine (Flax Trust), undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - The Irish Independent Newspaper Clippings, 1961, 1973 (Box Shared Tamiment 081, Folder 18)
  - Irish Images: Misty Places and Tranquil Light (Tom Quinn Kumpf), 2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The Irish People Newspaper Clippings, 1998 (Box Shared Tamiment 081, Folder 19)
  - The Irish Press Newspaper Clippings, 1961-1975, 1994 (Box Shared Tamiment 081, Folder 14, Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 10)
  - The Irish Repertory Theatre, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The Irish Voice Newspaper Clippings, 2003-2006 (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 6)
  - The Irish Volunteer Newsletter, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - "John Paul II: Young People of Ireland I Love You", 1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Kennedy Child Study Center Programs, 1997-2005 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Kevin Kennedy Business Cards, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Keys, undated (Box 6)
  - Knights of Columbus, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Knock Shrine Annual, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Loyola School Luncheon, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Marathon Medal, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Mars London Marathon Medal, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Martin Lyons, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - The Mass in Central Park, His Holiness Pope John Paul II, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Mass of Christian Burial, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Mass of Installation, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Mayo Football Club of New York, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - The Mayor's Liberty Awards, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Membership Articles, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Memorial Mass for Captain James Haggerty, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - The Merchants Club, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Mission Magazine, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Music Under the Lights, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Neighborhood Coalition for Shelter, Inc., 1996 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1961-2007 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - New York City Police Anchor Club, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "New York Guide Touristique et Carte" (NYC Map in French), 1964-1965 (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 12)
  - Notebook, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - NY State Council Knights of Columbus, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - NYPD Emerald Society presents "Irish Heritage in Policing", 2000 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Official Program - St. Patrick's Day Parade Celebration, 1987 (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 13)
  - Ordination of Bishops, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Ordination to the Sacred Priesthood, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Our Lady of Peace Church, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Out of Ireland, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - "Over the Rainbow" - A Tribute to Yip Harburg, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Patrick Brennan, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Paul Higgins, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Pioneer Centenary Rally Souvenir Program, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Pioneer Total Abstinence Ass'n of the Sacred Heart, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - "The Pope's Historic Visit" - Newsweek Magazine, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - The Pope's Visit (Time Life), undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Portincula Hospital, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Prayer Cards, 1988-2004 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Pro-Union Slate Buttons, undated
  - Religious Booklets, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - "A Remembrance of Colonel Patrick Kelly of the Irish Brigade", undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Reverand John J. Brown Testimonial Dinner-Dance, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Ribbon - "Appoint American Special Envoy to Northern Ireland", undated (Box 6)
  - Rice High School Yearbook, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Richmond Rugby Football Club, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Right Rev Msgr. James Horan, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Rural Housing Organisation, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The Sacrament of Confirmation, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Sacred Liturgy to Celebrate the Twenty-Fifth Wedding Anniversary of Bridie T. and Timothy V. Hartnett, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Saint Andrew's Society of the State of New York Annual Spring Tartan Ball, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook, undated (Box 27, Box 28)
  - Seamus Conroy, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Sean MacDermott, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Sketches, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - St. Brendan's Church, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - St. Patrick's Day Bing Crosby Decca Recording Program, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, 1983, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade and Celebration Committee, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Steering Wheel, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick, 1988-1997 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Solemn Eucharistic Celebration for the Progress of Peoples, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Sudden Impact, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Terence Cardinal Cooke, 1995, 1999, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Tribute to Siobhan McKenna, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - United Irish Counties Association of New York, Inc., 1982 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - United Irish Counties Dinner Menu, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Visitor: Ireland's Premier Tourist Magazine, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Series II: Photographs and Photo Negatives, 1916-2008 (inclusive); 1977-2008 (bulk); 21.67 Linear Feet in 20 record cartons
  This series contains photographs and photo negatives covering a variety of subjects such as: St. Patrick's Day Parades, Ancient Order of the Hibernians events, United Irish Counties events, Knight of Columbus events, Ireland, Irish football clubs, weddings, and church events.
  The collection also contains photographs of Mayor Ed Koch, Gerry Adams, Governor Mario Cuomo, Governor George Pataki, and President Bill Clinton.
  - 7:V 100 Mondes, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 21 Club Grand Marshal, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 42 W 44 Bar Assoc, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 168 Ave B, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 200 Park Ave & Joe Crowly Harbour Lights, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 201 East 83rd St NY, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 1011 First Ave, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 1011 First Ave Cardinal Cooke Mass, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1916 Massers Gaelic Park, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - A.A. Club, Grand Marshal, Bill Hynn, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - A.B.S., 2006 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Adrian Flannery, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Alex, Scarsdale, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Allied Irish Bank, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Allied Irish Bank, K of C, Co. Roscommon, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - A.I.M.S., 1995 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - A.I.M.S. Assoc, Towerview Gr., 1994 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - A.I.M.S. & Co. Sligo, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - A.I.M.S. Music, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - A.I.M.S. Private, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - A.I.M.S., Yonkers Rockway, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Airport, Old Planes, & Mount Rushmore, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Anchor Club, Marina del Ray, Police, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Anna McElroy, Woodside Steak House, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Antons Irish American Teamster Assoc, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - A.O.H., 1995-1996, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - A.O.H. Breckford, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - A.O.H. Breakfast, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - A.O.H. Bronx, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - A.O.H. Bronx, Co. Monaghan, Co. Lutrie, & A.I.M.S., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - A.O.H. Co. Board, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - A.O.H. Co. Board Breakfast Trophys, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - A.O.H. Co. Louth, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - A.O.H. Dinner, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - A.O.H. Dinner, Brooklyn, Mineola, Parade, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - A.O.H. Div 3, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - A.O.H. Div 4 & Div 3 Ladies, undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - A.O.H. Div 9th, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - A.O.H. Div 29, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - A.O.H. Div 29 and Keany, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - A.O.H. Durrows, undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - A.O.H. Glendale, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - A.O.H. & L.A.O.H., 1998 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - A.O.H. Mass & Breakfast, 1991, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - A.O.H., Mike Keaver, Bronx, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Archbishop Neary, undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Ardsley, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Armagh, undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Armory 26th, Brian O'Dwyer, Galway, Grogans, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Assemblyman Joe Crowley, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Astorian Manor, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Auntons Pole, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - B&W, Col UIC, Brooklyn, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - B&W Gaelic Park, St. Joseph Church, G.M.A. Breakfast, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - B&W GP Towers V, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - B&W Mayo, Sligo, Tional Assoc, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - B&W UIC & Mineola, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Ballina, Co. Mayo, Galway Dunmore Cheever, undated (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Ballinaszoe & Cong, Co. Mayo, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Bank, Gaelic Park, Co. Roscommor, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Bank of Ireland, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Bank of Ireland, Bro McCartin, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Bank of Ireland, Cardinal O'Connor, undated (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Bank of Ireland Echo & Voyage, undated (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Bank of Ireland, K of C, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Banquet Guests, undated (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Bar Assoc, undated (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Battery Park, Hour Children, undated (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Bellmont Festival, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Bellmurph, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Bellow Sean McManus, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Beth Oliver O'Donnell, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Biaggo, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Bill Burk, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Bill Burke, Co. Louth, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Bill Clinton, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Bill Colbert, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Birthday Party, Dunwoody & East River, Dunmore, Galway, St. Joseph's Church, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Birthday Party, Graig, Dunmore, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Bishop, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Bishop O'Connor, St. Stephens, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Bishop Mansell, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Bishop P. Flynn, Wedding, Gaelic Park, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Bone Marrow for Leukaemia, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Borough Hall Brooklyn, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Boston, 1995-2008 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Boston Christmas, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Breahon Law Society, Manhattan Club, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Brede McManus, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Brehon Law Society, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Brenda Kearns & Bradie McManus, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Brennan's Party, St. Josephs, Gaelic Park, St. Patricks Columbus Day, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Brennans Wedding, McElroy, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Brennan's Wedding, Tresa O'Malleys, East River, St. Patrick's Day, Xmas Party, St. Joseph's School, Dobbs Ferry, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Brian Boru's Pub, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Brian O'Dwire, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Brian O'Dwyer, 1995-1997 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Brian O'Durns Manhattan Club, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - BR Laurances Dance, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Bro. Clem House, Co. Louth Football, Martin Kearns, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Bro Clementia Party, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Bronx, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Brooklyn, 1991-2008 (Box 8, Folder 35-36)
  - Brooklyn A.O.H., 1991 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Brooklyn B&W, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Brooklyn Bridge, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Brooklyn Camogie, 1992-1997 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Brooklyn, Co. Carlow, Offally, 1989-1992 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Brooklyn, Co. Mayo, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Brooklyn, Dinkins, Moloney Rory Dolan, St. Patrick's, Dunmore, Glynns, Jake's Salon, K of C, Manahttan Club, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Brooklyn, Father Patrick, Co. Cavan, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Brooklyn Football, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Brooklyn Football Dance (B&W), undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Brooklyn, Galway City, Dunmore, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Brooklyn K. McDonaghy, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Brooklyn Mass, Parade, and Police, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Brooklyn, Mayo, 2007-2008 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Brooklyn & NYC, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Parade, 1986-1994 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Parade, Co. Tipperary, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn Parade Meeting, 1988-1999 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Brooklyn Parade, New York City Parade, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn Parade, Tipp Dance, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - California, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Calvery, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Calvery Cemetery, 1992, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Calvery Cemetery Boston, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Calvary Cemetery, Div 3 AOH, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Calvery Cemetery, K of C, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Camogie, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Camogie Boston, 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Camogie, Bruce Morrison, Tara Circle, & Eileen, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Camogie Dance (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Camogie & Minor Board, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Camogie Self, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Camogie Towers, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Camogie, Tower View Center, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Camogie Van Cortlandt Park, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Canada, The Great Hunger, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Canada, Tim Pat Coogan, Bishop, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Car Dept Police, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Car Push from Galway City to Tuam in August, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Cars, Emerald, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Cardinal Cook, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Cardinal Cook Dinner, Frank Durkin, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Cardinal Cook Guild, K of C, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Cardinal Cooke Mass, 1994, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Cardinal Cooke Mass, UIC, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Cardinal O'Connor, UIC Festival, Div 3 AOH, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Carlow, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Carlow Brooklyn Parade, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Castle Bar Co. Mayo Co. Cork, undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Castle Harbour Casino Police, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Cavan (?), 2007 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Cavan T. Duggan, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Cavan, Tipp, Parade, Galway Parade Meeting, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Cemetery (?), 2008 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Charitable Contributions, undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Christening, Mineola, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - City Council, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - City Hall, 1994-1998 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - City Hall, Manhattan Club, Cody McCane, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - City Hall, Mayor Koch, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Clare Hurleny, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Clarke, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Clinton Gore, undated (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Clinton Gore Meeting, undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Co. Board A.O.H., 1996 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Co. Board Breakfast A.O.H. 38th Park Ave, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Co. Board Football Dance, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Co. Carlow, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Co. Carlow, Bar Assoc, Co. Kerry, & St. Patrick, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Co. Cavan, 1984-1997 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Co. Cavan's Association, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Co. Cavan and Co. Roscommon, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Co Cavan Football, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Co. Cavan Football Dinner Dance, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Co. Cavan Group, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Co. Cavan Meetings, Jerusalem, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Co. Cavan Woodside, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Co. Clare, 1987-1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Co. Clark, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Co. Cork, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Co. Derry, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Co. Derry, J. Duinleavy, Terrance on the Park, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 15)